Contact

sayedelgholy81@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/sayed-gomaa (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

C++

Java

Python (Programming Language)

Languages

Arabic

English

Certifications

Structuring Machine Learning Projects

Convolutional Neural Networks

Neural Networks and Deep Learning

Data Analysis Professional Nanodegree Program

Improving Deep Neural Networks: Hyperparameter Tuning, Regularization and Optimization

Honors-Awards

ENTREPRENEURIAL IDEA GENERATION CAMP

ICPC-programing competition

Sayed Goma

Machine Learning | Deep Learning Engineer | Helwan

Summary

I'm a student at the Faculty of Engineering, Helwan University, Computer Engineering department. I have worked professionally with C programming, Python Programming, and C++, I also have fair experience in data analyst, machine learning, and Deep Learning. and I participate in programming competitive Acpc contest

Experience

Emarat Al-Ard Research Centre for Sustainable Development
Machine Learning Engineer

June 2021 - Present (7 months)

June 2021 - Present (7 months)

London

Tasks:

- -Develop programs in Python
- -Investigate a dataset using Python data analysis
- -collect data using selenium scraping
- -Perform the entire data analysis process on a dataset
- -gather data from multiple sources in a variety of formats

Education

Helwan University Cairo

Bachelor's degree, Computer Engineering · (October 2017 - June 2022)